azmovies.net 2011-11-26

# Privacy Policy - AZ Movies

## Privacy Policy and Disclaimer

_\- AZ Movies (“AZ Movies”, “we”, “us”, “our”, “www.azmovies.net”) wants you to be fully aware of what happens to the personal information we collect through your use of our website located at www.azmovies.net (“AZ Movies”).-_

### Copyright Notification

_Material contained on this website is copyrighted and owned by the respective owners. The materials are used for promotional purpose only. All trademarks and trade names are the properties of their respective owners._

AZ Movies does not permit copyright infringing activities and infringement of intellectual property rights on its website, and will remove all content if properly notified that such content infringes on another's intellectual property rights. 

_Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, by using AZ Movies , you signify your agreement to this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended and/or revised at any time. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the AZ Movies._

#### Do We Collect Personal Information ?

* * *

AZ Movies uses “cookies” and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there.  
Cookies are pieces of information that a website either transfers to your computer's hard drive or stores temporarily in your computer's memory for record-keeping purposes. 

We may permit advertising on our website by third parties and/or link to the websites of third parties that are not owned or operated by AZ Movies. These third parties may independently solicit and collect personal information, send their own cookies to our visitors, or link visitors away from our site. They may also use collected data differently than AZ Movies.

#### DoubleClick DART Cookie

* * *

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.azmovies.net Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.azmovies.net and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, TribalFusion. 

#### Use Of Personal Information

* * *

Any personal information that you provide us by visiting AZ Movies is only used for the purposes of: internal record keeping and providing you with the services offered through our website. 

#### Sharing Information

* * *

AZ Movies does not buy or sell consumer information. We don`t share any of the information collected. We reserve the right to transfer any personal information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets.

#### Offensive or inappropriate content

* * *

If you post or send offensive, inappropriate or objectionable content anywhere on or to AZ Movies we may use your personal information to stop such behavior, that means we can ban your ip so you cannot post on this site.

#### External Links

* * *

AZ Movies may contain links to, or advertisements about, non-AZ Movies websites. Other sites may also reference, advertise, or link to AZ Movies. AZ Movies does not endorse or sponsor other websites, is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of non-AZ Movies sites, expressly disclaims any statements or assertions made on such websites, and denies all liability associated with your use of, and the content on, such other websites and advertisements. 

#### Contact us for privacy policy questions

* * *

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy you can contact us at this email : contact[at]azmovies.net or you can use the contact page. The Privacy Policy may change from time to time so we advice you to check it any time you visit our site.
